# SUDHIR KUMAR THANNA () Featured

Salesforce Software Developer seeking roles Salesforce Design, Salesforce Development, Requirement Gathering, Software Development, Requirement Analysis, Testing, Application Design, Core Java, Angular Js, Python, JIRA, SpringBoot, Jenkins, Toad, Aura Lightnin



Current Designation: Salesforce Software Developer Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Current Company: PwC (Price water House Coopers S.p.A) Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Business Administration]

Current Location: milan

Pref. Location: Hyderabad, Dubai, Germany

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Salesforce Software Developer, Salesforce Design, Salesforce Development, Requirement Gathering, Software

Development, Requirement Analysis, Testing, Application Design, Core Java, Angular Js,

Python, JIRA, SpringBoot, Jenkins, Toad, Aura Lightning

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

## Summary

A technocrat and Certified 5x Salesforce Developer offering, over 5 years of National & International experience in Salesforce, Core Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Angular JS, UI Automation, Testing, Spring Boot, J2EE and Rest Web Services Skilled in overall salesforce development life-cycle involving requirement analysis, system study, designing, testing, programming, coding, de-bugging, defect management, status reporting & documentation

Excellent track record of designing customized application for a wide range of clients

Keen analyst with excellence in gathering and understanding requirements of clients & other multiple stakeholders, followed by translation into functional specifications as well as provisioning of customized software solution

Worked within a focused agile team to develop applications and platform features

Skills in programming with APEX, Triggers, JavaScript, HTML, XML, and related technologies

## **Work Experience**

# **PwC (Price water House Coopers S.p.A)** as Salesforce Software Developer Jun 2019 to Till Date

Working with the team namely 'Tech Extended'; hands-on experience in CRM Technologies including Salesforce Platform Developer, Apex, LWC, Aura, Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, JQuery, Git, Jenkins, IntelliJ, Visual Studio and AngularJS Worked on shell project; performed configuration of salesforce

Understanding the functional workflows and explaining it to the team; developing the business logic and ensuring proper implementation of the same

Domain knowledge on Enterprise Design Pattern; adhering to the standard of code patterns for writing the code Worked on the 'Shell Energy Project'; utilized marketing cloud tool 'Evergage' that altered the UI of web page used for marketing and tracking the customers as well as conducted an in-depth analysis of page traffic flow and different types of users from different platforms such as FB, Google, Instagram

Successfully configured UI for diverse customers from multiple sources

Gained rich knowledge on various methods of programming as per the project requirements

Utilizing SFDC to improve processes and productivity, and making recommendations to support an organization scaling at a rapid pace

Ensuring the best possible performance, quality, and responsiveness of applications

Analyzing and assisting in defining specifications and user requirements

Developing, maintaining, and executing test procedures for applications & system

Utilizing latest tools and keeping up to date with technology changes

1/22/2021

Providing technical assistance and end user troubleshooting for bug fixes, enhancements, and "how-to" assistance Working with management, creating and managing complex workflow rules, data validation, and triggers Gained experience in Web Service Callouts like Rest and SOAP API development, AWS, Yandex, Magento, Salesforce Web service callouts for integrations and deployments from other third party cloud services to fetch, analyze data and create objects using these web services

Developing the Zelig HomePage using the LwC in Candy Project

#### MiMoto Milan as Software Engineer

Mar 2019 to Jun 2019

Engaged in design & development of test cases

Conducted an in-depth testing of the Admin Page, Android Application as well as features of iOS Application Performed integration on IoT Devices as well as configuration on Amazon AWS

#### Model N Software India Pvt. Ltd. as member of Technical Staff

Jun 2015 to Sep 2018

Gained extensive exposure in working on various technologies such as Java, JavaScript, Automation, HTML, CSS, Performance Measure, SQL, Linux, Jenkins, Configurations, Framework Developer and IBM Cognos

Active involvement in numerous projects and enhancements, Bug Fixes; worked on Framework Development in the Core Business Development Team of Model N

Dealt with various clients including Merck, Novartis, J&J and BMS

Successfully led integration of two different enterprise standard codes for producing a single one using a new framework development following spring boot framework and development of internal SQIN (Software Quality Initiative) Framework for testing and UI Automation; worked on Jenkins and BATAM Reporting

Gained experience in Jenkins, Deployment and Integration, and also UI Automation Development, Scripting of the UI Automation Scripts Proven excellence in dealing with Spring Boot, EJB, Hibernate, Selenium, UI Automation Framework as well as MVC Framework Development Working on different teams and a continuous learning and Integration (UBC/Payer Team, SQIN/Automation Team, Devops/BRE Team)

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Gayatri Vidya Parishad college of Engineering in 2015

PG: PG Diploma (Business Administration) from Welingkar Institute of Management Development & Research in 2018

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Core Java, Salesforce, J2EE, JavaScript	
Apex, LWC, Aura Lightning	
Spring Boot, Angular Js, Python	
SpringBoot, Spring, REST	
SOAP Web Services	
Enterprise Design Patterns	
HTML, CSS	
SQL, Oracle, Maria DB	
RDBMS, Toad for MySQL	
IntelliJ IDEA, SQL Developer	
Eclipse, Visual Studio, GIT	
MS Office, FileZilla, WinSCP	
JIRA, SD Tracker	
Jenkins	

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=5461eb6891a659349477b7b6be220cca0b550c51484008165018445d5...

Linux and Windows	
HP UFT, Test Complete, Katalon	

# Languages Known

Lang	guage	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
Engl	ish				
Italia	an				

## **Affirmative Action**

Category: General

Physically Challenged: No

## **Work Authorization**

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time